Name: Yeung Pok Hei

Email address: pyeung23@my.centennialcollege.ca

# **Summary of Qualification:**

I have graduated from Bachelor of Science (Honors) in Food Science and Safety
programme at the Technological and High Education Institute of Hong Kong and
have my first job in the qc team and laboratory team of Vitagreen, a leading
pharmaceutical and health product company in Hong Kong, which allows me gain
precious experience.

#### **Education:**

9/2016-6/2020:

Technological and Higher Education Institute of Hong Kong (Bachelor of Science (Honors) in Food Science and Safety)

9/2010-6/2016:

Christ College (F1-F6)

## **Experience:**

6/2020-until now

Vitagreen (Junior qc assistant, Lab assistant, Junior laboratory technician)

Junior qc assistant:

- In line sampling
- Raw material sampling
- In process qc
- Cleaning validation

Lab assistant & Assistant Laboratory Technician

- Conducting test including Microbiological test, TLC, UV, dissolution test, TOC
- Managing SOP (make sure all control copies are available)
- Method development for new raw material
- Writing and updating SOP

## 6/2019-8/2019:

Internship at Chen Zhou Zhan Xiang Green Agricultural Limited

- Participating in agriculture works in the farm
- Held sharing section on ISO 22000 and GMP for their staff
- Research on the extraction of chlorogenic acid from honeysuckle for the development of edible film coating of the oranges that are produced in the farm.

### 6/2018-9/2018:

Retail Associate at ToysRus

#### 6/2017-9/2017:

Retail Associate at ToysRus

- Providing services to customers including assisting and problem-solving
- Keeping the goods either on floor or in the warehouse nice and tidy

## **Honours and Awards:**

2016:

Trinity College London Grade 7 Rock & Pop Bass

### Skill:

# **Laboratory Testing - Microbiological test**

- Total bacteria count (TBC)
- Total yeast & mold count (TYMC)
- E.coli
- Pseudomonas aeruginosa
- Salmonella
- Staphylococcus aureus
- Gram stain

# **Laboratory Testing - Chemical test**

- Thin layer chromatography (TLC)
- UV spectrophotometer
- Anthrone test

## **General Programming, Web Development**

- C#
- Java
- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript

#### 3/2020:

Participate and Passed Exam of ISO 22000:2018 Lead Auditor Training Course organized by BSI Hong Kong

### **Volunteer Activities:**

29/10/2017 Inno Carnival 2017

 Held in Science park and I was one of the helper in the VTC booth, introducing the Coccoloba uvifera to the visitor.

24/11/2018 THE i info day 2018

 Held on 24/11/2018 in Tsing Yi Campus. I was one of the helper to help the visitor during the workshop and responsible for some preparation and cleaning up after the event.

Availability: July 2021

Reference available upon request